{
    "subject": "resource/Samsung_Galaxy_S6",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Samsung Galaxy S6 and Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge are Android smartphones manufactured and marketed by Samsung Electronics. The S6 and S6 Edge jointly serve as successors to the Galaxy S5. The smartphones were officially unveiled in a press conference at Mobile World Congress on 1 March 2015. Alongside the S6, Samsung also unveiled the S6 Edge, a variant whose screen is wrapped along the sides of the device; the curvature is usable for several additional features.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Samsung Galaxy S6 states that it and its variant Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge are Android smartphones manufactured and marketed by Samsung Electronics, serving as successors to Galaxy S5, and were officially unveiled at Mobile World Congress on March 1st, 2015.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8727989792823792,
            "question": "What were the Samsung Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge successors to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8519178628921509,
            "question": "When were the Samsung Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge officially unveiled?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459976315498352,
            "question": "Is the Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge a variant of the Samsung Galaxy S6?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567315697669983,
            "question": "Which event marked the official introduction of the Samsung Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6896523237228394,
            "question": "What type of devices are the Samsung Galaxy S6 and Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5907921195030212,
            "question": "Where was the unveiling of the Samsung Galaxy S6 series held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.522933304309845,
            "question": "Which company manufactured and markets the Samsung Galaxy S6 series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4341992437839508,
            "question": "What operating system do the Samsung Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge run on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38884809613227844,
            "question": "Name the event where the Samsung Galaxy S6 series was first presented."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2987564206123352,
            "question": "What year did Samsung release the Galaxy S6 series?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Samsung Galaxy S6 states that it and its variant Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge are Android smartphones manufactured and marketed by Samsung Electronics, serving as successors to Galaxy S5, and were officially unveiled at Mobile World Congress on March 1st, 2015.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4990_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the event where the Samsung Galaxy S6 series was first presented.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4990_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What operating system do the Samsung Galaxy S6 and S6 Edge run on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4990_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company manufactured and markets the Samsung Galaxy S6 series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4990_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4990_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided information in the documents supports the statement that the Samsung Galaxy S6 and its variant, Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge, are Android smartphones manufactured and marketed by Samsung Electronics, serving as successors to the Galaxy S5, and were officially unveiled at Mobile World Congress on March 1st, 2015."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}